friv.io 2015-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Friv.io Friv.io

We value the confidentiality of our users’ personal information in high regard. We are devoted to collecting and utilizing our users’ personal data in a very responsible and trustworthy manner. Hence, we strive to provide you with utmost security and confidentiality at our website. This document will provide you with simple and understandable answers to your queries.

What is the information that is collected on this site?  
When browsing through our website, instances occur where we ask you to provide some personal information about you (the user). These should be voluntary provided by the user. These may or may not include your name, age, gender, contact address, zip code, telephone number.

In addition, our website also collects non-personally identifiable information which includes your IP Address, browser types, and operating systems information. We utilize all these data in making internal assessment about the functional levels of our site, as well as in enhancing the experience provided by the site to the user.

Because of the constant and numerous advances that occur with Internet technology, our Private Policy may also change frequently. We will prioritize notifying our users about the alterations/updates made through site announcements, primarily through email notifications.

Lastly, our website does not retain email addresses with commercial drive. We assure you that we do not divulge, share, or give away any information and emails from our users and any retentions of such are for purely technical reasons.

Will the website combine together the personal information provided by its users with offline information about these users?  
In instances where combination of these data would occur, we make it as an utmost priority that our users be notified immediately.

What are the security measures taken by the website to safeguard the security of the information provided by the customer?  
Our website takes pride in the utmost security and protection we provide to all the data and information related our users. We make use of various internal security mechanisms that protects the users’ personal information from any form of unauthorized means. We deploy various protective security measures which include firewall, anti viral software, passwords, etc. In addition, we also reinforce caution to our users who use public/shared computers that they remain vigilant in signing off every time finish using the said computers. We remind them also to be wary of various means of security breaching.

Is information from minors collected in this website?  
We do not collect any information from minors on this website. We encourage users who are below 18 years old to browse this site with adult supervision.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
